Guide to the Matt Gonzalez San Francisco City Supervisors' 2000 Election Files
Matt Gonzalez San Francisco city supervisors' 2000 election files,
2000-2002
M1332
Gonzalez, Matt.
1.5 linear ft. (2 manuscript boxes and 1 print box)
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Pre-election, election, and post-election materials relating to Matt Gonzalez's run for City and County of San Francisco Supervisor in 2000, including publicity, correspondence, subject files, and newspapers coverage.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 24 hours in advance of intended use.
Biography / Administrative History
On December 12, 2000, Gonzalez became the first member of the Green Party to win elective office in San Francisco, winning over 65% of the vote in a run-off election. He was elected to the San Francisco Board of Supervisors, representing District 5.
Scope and Content of Collection
Pre-election, election, and post-election materials relating to Matt Gonzalez's run for City and County of San Francisco Supervisor in 2000, including publicity, correspondence, subject files, and newspapers coverage.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Subjects
Gonzalez, Matt.; San Francisco (Calif.)--Politics and government.
Collection Contents
- Election campaign material: Matt Gonzalez for supervisor and District Attorney, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Election campaign material: Juanita Owens and others, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Election - information, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Green Party, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Matt Gonzalez correspondence, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Poetry for Matt Gonzalez, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Health care, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Housing / HUD / Ronnie Davis case, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Energy / Utilities / Pacific Gas & Electric, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Juvenile justice, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Treasure island, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- San Francisco Supervisor meeting materials, 2001 Feb. - Mar. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- San Francisco Supervisor meeting materials, 2001 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Newspaper clippings, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Newspaper - articles & letters Matt Gonzalez for District Attorney, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- The Superior Court of the State of California in and for the City and County of San Francisco, In re: Matt Gonzalez, court reporters transcript of contempt proceedings, 2000 Jan. 12 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous legal materials, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Art, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Text / articles, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Jeff Adachi, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Newspapers, 2000 (Flat-box 3)
- Campaign flyers, 2000 (Flat-box 3)